http://www.tireguru.net/privacy_policy.php

Privacy Policy
Your privacy and your trust are important to us!
This website, tireguru.net (“Website”), is owned and operated by American Business Management Systems, Inc. (“ABMS”) Developers of Tire Guru Software, Websites and More!
ABMS may collect personal and non-personal information on this Website. This privacy statement describes and explains to users our practices concerning information
collected from this Website.
Information Collected and Use
You have complete control over your personal information and can visit our Website without providing us with any personal information. Our Website is designed to inform
interested users about ABMS companies and products, and to collect certain contact information from such users Including but not limited to name, company, email address,
and phone number. The submission of personal information is voluntary. We may use the personal information that we collect for various purposes including:
To contact a user about their business and their interest level of our products;
In our internal surveys, to obtain feedback on our products, our Website, or on other aspects of our business; and
To send promotional or informational materials and news at no charge.
All information is confidential and will never be sold or rented to any other party. Data may be shared if required by state or federal law or if the requesting company’s
best interest might be serviced by one of our partner or sister companies. If you have any questions about this policy, please contact us.
About Tire Guru
At Tire Guru Software, Websites and More we develop and support state of the art point of sale
and business management software, ecommerce websites, digital vehicle inspections, and more.
We are fully committed to the tire and automotive industry and to providing state of the art
leading edge products for Tire Dealers, Auto Repair Shops, and Tire Wholesale Distributors.
We strive to bring new and innovative products and technology to our customers year after year.
Tire Guru employees are focused on building a one-stop complete business solution platform.
We are proud to provide products that truly give our customers a competitive advantage in the market place.
